{
  "LevelId": 25,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 249,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "EQUIPMENT",
      "question": "commonly used to refer to tools, machinery, or supplies used for a particular purpose or activity"
    },
    {
      "id": 250,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "CLAMBAKES",
      "question": "cooking of shellfish, typically by roasting or steaming them over an open fire"
    },
    {
      "id": 251,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "CARPETBAG",
      "question": "bag is often associated with the historical term"
    },
    {
      "id": 252,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "CORYPHAEI",
      "question": "dominates a group, especially in intellectual or artistic pursuits"
    },
    {
      "id": 253,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "CIRCKETER",
      "question": "sports professional plays cricket and is known as a"
    },
    {
      "id": 254,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BLOWLAMPS",
      "question": "devices are commonly used for heating or soldering and are known as"
    },
    {
      "id": 255,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "FLASHBACK",
      "question": "term is used to describe a sudden and vivid recollection of a past event or experience"
    },
    {
      "id": 256,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "ADVOCATED",
      "question": "the term for someone who publicly supports or recommends a particular cause or policy"
    },
    {
      "id": 257,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "VACANCIES",
      "question": "you call the positions or job openings that a company is actively looking to fill"
    },
    {
      "id": 258,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "JAUNDICED",
      "question": "yellowish of the skin,whites of the eyes caused by increased levels of bilirubin in the blood"
    },
    {
      "id": 259,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BABIRUSAS",
      "question": "rare and distinctive mammals with curving tusks are native to the Indonesian"
    },
    {
      "id": 260,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "MATHEMATICS",
      "question": "subject involves the study of numbers, quantities, and shapes"
    }
  ]
}